

Gabriel Brodersen

MSc in IT, Software Design iOS Developer

36 Years

brodersen@me.com @

+45 26362213

Copenhagen, Denmark @

linkedin.com/in/gabrielbrodersen/ @

About Me

I'm a software developer who recently graduated from the IT University of Copenhagen with a master's degree in software development. My specialization and passion is in iOS development and the Apple ecosystem of technologies. My post-university work background is in UX & UI Design primarily for mobile apps. I'm passionate about technology that improve people's lives and I'm always striving to learn and improve. And I • coding in .

Work Experience

Owner, Freelance UX & UI designer GB Company

Jan. 2013 - Sept. 2020

Communication & IT Chora Connection

Sept. 2017 - Nov. 2018

UX & UI Designer DigDuck IVS

May 2015 - Mar. 2018

UX Consultant Newsquid ApS

July 2013 – Mar. 2014

UX & UI Designer LUCUS ApS

Aug. 2013 - June 2014

Webdeveloper XOTC IVS

Feb. 2013 - Sept. 2013

UX & UI Designer Gedda-Headz A/S

Feb. 2009 - Dec. 2012

Industrial Designer & 3D Modeler MOEF A/S

Sept. 2006 - Dec. 2008

Competencies

iOS and WatchOS Development, Xcode, Swift, Apple Frameworks incl. SwiftUI, Combine, etc., MVVM, Reactive and Declarative Programming, Software Architecture, Java, Python, JavaScript, Web Front-End Development, REST APIs, Git, Firebase, UX & UI Design, HCI, Technical Interaction Design, Agile.

Education

MSc in Information Technology, Software Design IT University of Copenhagen 2019 – 2021

BSc in Digital Media & Design IT University of Copenhagen 2016 – 2019

Multimediadesign Roskilde Technical School & KEA 2004 – 2005

High School Øregård Gymnasium 2001–2004

Other Work

Voluntary Coding Pirates Feb. 2019 – Aug. 2019

Voluntary

Feb. 2016 – Feb. 2017

SIND Ungdom

Languages

Danish | Native

English | Professional working proficiency